var STARTING_CARDS = [
  { front: '一 (K)', back: 'one/line radical' },
  { front: '一つ', back: 'ひとつ<br/>one thing' },
  { front: 'もう一度', back: 'もういちど<br/>one more time!' },

  { front: '度 (K)', back: 'times' },
  { front: '(xxx) 度 (にyyy)', back: 'たび<br/>Every time xxx happens, yyy happens.' },

  { front: '緒 (K)', back: 'together' },
  { front: '一緒に', back: 'いっしょに<br/>together' },

  { front: '人', back: 'ひと<br/>person' },
  { front: 'xxx人', back: 'xxxじん<br/>person from xxx country - France人, America人 etc.' },
  { front: '一人で', back: 'ひとりで<br/>one person, alone' },

  // COVERED //
  { front: '般 (K)', back: 'general/overall' },
  { front: '一般に', back: 'いっぱんに<br/>generally, commonly' },

  { front: '的 (K)', back: 'motivation/"-al"' },
  { front: 'xxx的', back: 'xxxてき<br/>modifier that turns a noun into an adjective;<br/>politics -> political, education -> educational' },
  { front: '一般的な', back: 'いっぱんてきな<br/>ordinary, as in non-special' },

  { front: '日', back: 'ひ<br/>a day' },
  { front: '一日', back: 'ついたち<br/>first day of the month' },

  { front: '番 (K)', back: 'number'},
  { front: '一番', back: 'いちばん<br/>number one, the best' }
];
